Hello friends, in today's video we will talk about
address not found, if you send an
email to someone and an error comes there,
whether you send an email on your mobile or on
your computer laptop in which you are sending the
email and if you get an error of
address not found, then how will you
solve it, you should watch this video completely,
in this we will tell you the total steps,
let's start friends, let me tell you that
here you can see that an error has come in my email
and we will talk about this error,
where there is an error you can see address
not found, so if in your mail which you have
forwarded to someone and you have such a
problem, then how will you solve it, I will
give you total information in this video, friends my name is Vikas Kumar and let me
tell you that whenever you send an email to someone, if
you make any mistake even for a single word in the address, then
you will get to see this error,
whether you are sending an
email from your mobile or from your laptop
or from your computer, then
always be careful with this  As you can see,
I have taken a screenshot here
and you will see here that the
address is not found. After this, you can see that
I have given @gmail, so this address
is not found. So what should you do always,
if you look at it from here, then if
you want to forward it again from here, you
can forward it from here,
but you should always keep one thing in mind
that you have to carefully check every word of your email ID
because if any of your
email IDs have a large number of
digits, then you face this problem. So
what should you do, you should do this again, whatever error you have got,
you have to send that error again from your email. So,
I will show you, I
will open my Gmail, after it opens, you
can see here that this is the
error that has come. What should you do, you have to click on it. After
clicking like this, you can see here that this is the
kind of error that has come. Now, if you
want, from here, you can forward it again by clicking on the three dots.
What
you have to do here is see here it is written reply all
and there is a forward written so you have to
click on forward, you
can see here now I will go back a little,
see here this kind of option is given
here you have many options
like if you want to delete
this mail from here, you
can delete it from here and if you
feel that I did everything right here
but the email id which we had given is
wrong then what you have to do is
click on the three dots and
click on forward from here as soon as you click on forward
your email id will again appear
here what you have to do is
tap from here and again you will
type all your mails here and this time you have to send
it by entering the correct address as you send it earlier
your
email will be forwarded to 110 if you
like this video and like it I
want to see more such technical videos
please subscribe to the channel and press the bell icon as well
Please do so, we will meet again in the next video. Jai
Hind
Vande Mataram